A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art AAA.finccoll
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; 14.8 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25
  - "Art Deco" (1970) (Box 6)
    - Loans, 1970 (Box 7)
      - Louis Winter, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 23
    - Research, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 32-34)
    - Slide Script by American Craft Council, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Traveling Exhibition (Box 7)
      - Loan Agreements, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 36-38)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 39-44)
      - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - "Art from Belgium" (1965) (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 46-47)
    - Lists, circa 1964 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - "Art from Belgium" (1965) (Box 8)
    - Printed Material and Photographs, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Art from Finland" (1973) (Box 8)
    - Catalog and Clippings, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Oversized clipping housed in box 22, folder 3
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4-8)
    - Insurance and Loan Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10-15)
  - "Art from the Chase Manhattan Bank Collection" (1971) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Art in Jewelry" (1966) (Box 8)
    - Artist Files (Box 8)
      - Gordon Andrews, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Friedrich Becker, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
      - Georges Braque, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Maurice Brault, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Roberto Burle-Marx, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Salvador Dali, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Bert Gore, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Gubelin (Martha Widmer), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
      - Paula Haivaoja, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Anne Kursmo, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Octave Landuyt, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Ole Lynggard, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Bruno Martinazzi, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Marianne Ostier, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
      - Gillian Packard, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Sigurd Persson, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Antonio Pineda, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Sepp Schmoelzer, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Reiko Yamada, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Biographies, 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Catalog and Press Release, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1966 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 43-46)
    - Customs, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
    - Lists, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Photographs, circa 1966 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Printers, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Painting" (1965) (Box 8)
    - Artist's Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      Contains handwritten artist statements by Jim Dine, Grace Hartigan, George Ortman, Jack Sonenberg, Reva Urban, and Jack Youngerman.
    - Biographies, circa 1965 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Painting" (1965) (Box 9)
    - Insurance Evaluations, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Lists, circa 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and Source Material, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure" (1966) (Box 9)
    - Artist Files (Box 9)
      - Possibilities, circa 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Stephen Antonakos, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Richard Artschwager, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Richard Baringer, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Mary Bauermeister, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Chryssa, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Dan Flavin, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Paul Frazier, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Charles Hinman, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Will Insley, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Donald Judd, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Lyman Kipp, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Sol Le Witt, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Sven Lukin, circa 1966 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Victor Millonzi, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Robert Morris, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Otto Piene, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Robert Smithson, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Robert Watts, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - John Willenbacher, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Catalog, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Photographs for Catalog, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Photographs of Exhibition, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
    - Press Release and Exhibition Announcement, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Motion Picture Film of Exhibition Installation, 1966; 1 Film reels Original; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Duplicate; 1 Videocassettes (Digital Betacam) Duplicate (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Videocassettes are duplicate access copies of motion picture film. Original film reel stored off-site.
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage" (1967) (Box 9)
    - Artist Files (Box 9)
      - Marcelo Bonevardi, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Martha Bourdrez, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Mario Ceroli, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - John Day, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Perle Fine, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Fitzia, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Elias Friedensohn, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Edward Giobbi, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 43)
        Oversized posters housed in OV 24
      - Sita Gomez de Kaneba, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 44)
        Oversized posters housed in OV 23
      - Al Hansen, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Ray Johnson, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 46)
        Contains correspondence and mail art by Ray Johnson.
      - Roy Lichtenstein, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Conrad Marca-Relli, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Richard Merkin, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 49)
        Contains mail art by the artist.
      - Richard Miller, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Armando Morales, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Claes Oldenburg, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - George Ortman, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Alfonso Ossorio, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 54)
        Oversized poster housed in OV 24
      - Paul Pollaro, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - David Porter, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Joe Raffaele, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Eduardo Ramirez, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Robert Rauschenberg, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Larry Rivers, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Sebold, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Harry Soviak, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Theodoros Stamos, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Paul Tschinkel, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 64)
        Oversized poster in OV 24.
      - Esteban Vicente, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Linda Vivona, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Paul Waldman, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
    - Lists, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Photographs of Artists, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Photographs of Exhibition, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Traveling Exhibition, American Federation of Arts, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - "Art in Process IV" (1969-1970) (Box 9)
    - Artist Files (Box 9)
      - Carl Andre, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 76)
      - Lynda Benglis, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 77)
        Contains the poetry chapbook "Identikit" by Jim Brodey.
      - Mel Bochner, circa 1969 (Box 9, Folder 78)
        Contains an interview of Bochner conducted by Elayne Varian, found on one sound tape reel with accompanying transcript. Also contains photocopied writings on Bochner's measurement pieces, photographs of the artist with his work, and an open letter of complaint regarding the installation of a work at the New York Cultural Center.
      - Bill Bollinger, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - Rafael Ferrer, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - Barry Flanagan, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Artist Files (Box 10)
      - Eva Hesse, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Robert Morris, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Robert Morris (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Contains installation instructions.
      - Bruce Nauman, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Robert Ryman, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Richard Serra, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Richard Van Buren, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Lawrence Weiner, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
        Contains a copy of the artist's book, Statements (1968)
    - Artist Statements, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Catalog, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Oversized galleys housed in OV 24.
    - Correspondence and Clippings, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Research, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
      Contains photocopy of typed transcript of a discussion involving Carl Andre, Dan Graham, Lawrence Wiener and others. Also contains a photocopy typescript draft of an essay by Dan Graham entitled "Subject Matter I."
    - Wall Text, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Art in Process V" (1972) (Box 10)
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Notes and Receipts, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Photographs of Artwork, Sol LeWitt, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Photographs of Installation, Contact Sheets, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Installation, Prints, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 23-25)
  - "Art in Series" (1967-1968) (Box 10)
    - Artist Résumés, circa 1967 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Artist Statements, circa 1967 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Oversized clippings in OV 24.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
    - Letters of Request for Loans, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Notes and Gallery Visitor Count, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Writings, Photocopies, circa 1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Contains a variety of unattributed writings including poetry, descriptions of work, and a photocopy typescript of an essay by Mel Bochner entitled "The Serial Attitude."
    - Writings, Original Works by Dan Graham, circa 1966 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Contains three signed, typescript works including "Discrete Scheme without Memory," "Exclusion Principle," and "Poem."
  - "Art Nouveau" (1969) (Box 10)
    - Catalog and Inserts, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, General, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, Thank Yous, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence with Lenders, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 42-44)
    - Lists, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 46-53)
    - Photographs, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 54-56)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1969 (Box 10, Folder 57-58)
      Oversized photographs in OV 24.
    - Supper Dance Records, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - "Artists Select" (1964) (Box 10)
    - Artist Files (Box 10)
      - Leonard Baskin, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Carlos Basq, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Joe Brainard, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - James Brooks, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Paul Burlin, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Joseph Cornell, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Edwin Dickinson, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - L. Bock Dicosola, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Herbert Ferber, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Artist Files (Box 11)
      - Balcomb Greene, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Adolph Gottlieb, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Red Grooms, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Chaim Gross, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Philip Guston, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Edward Hill, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Ralph Humphrey, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        Oversized poster filed in OV 24.
      - Murray Israel, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Gillian Jagger, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Alfred Jensen, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Eddie Johnson, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Joe Jones, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Yayoi Kusama, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Ibram Lassaw, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Richard Lindner, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Richard Lippold, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Seymour Lipton, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Conrad Marca-Relli, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - David Milby, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Robert Motherwell, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Robert Murray, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Louise Nevelson, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Knud Nielsen, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Barnett Newman, 1964, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - I. Rice Pereira, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Alfonso Ossorio, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Anthony Padovano, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Ad Reinhardt, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Larry Rivers, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Theodore Roszak, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Cornelius Ruhtenberg, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Abby Shahn, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Ben Shahn, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Sewell Sillman, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Raphael Soyer, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Theodoros Stamos, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Pat Steir, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Joan Tausik, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Philipp Weichberger, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Charles Edward Wright, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Andrew Wyeth, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Paul Yakovenko, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Biographies, Master Artists, circa 1964 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Biographies, Young Artists, circa 1964 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Catalog, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Lists, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Photographs, Artists and Installation Views, circa 1964 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1964 (Box 11, Folder 49-51)
      Oversized photograph housed in OV 24.
    - Receipts, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - "Artists' Videotape Performances" (1971) (Box 11)
    - Budget and Invoices, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 54-55)
    - Lists, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Notes on Video Installation and Performance, circa 1971 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      See also correspondence for additional instructions from artists for the installation of their artworks. Oversized notes on Douglas Davis installation housed in OV 24
    - Photographs (Box 11)
      - Contact Sheets, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Negatives, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Prints and Transparencies, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 60-61)
    - Press Releases and Publicity, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      Oversized Magazine housed in OV 24.
    - Research, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Video Recordings (Box 11)
      - Vito Acconci and Kathy Dillon, "Remote Control", 1971; 2 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 11, Folder 64-65)
        Multi channel closed circuit video performance.
      - Douglas Davis, "Numbers", 1970-1972; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 11, Folder 66, Item 1)
      - Douglas Davis, "Sequences/Night Video", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 11, Folder 66, Item 2)
        Recorded artifact of interactive video and sound installation.
    - Video Recordings (Box 12)
      - Dan Graham, "Lax/Relax", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Dan Graham, "Roll", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 2, Item 1)
        Multi-channel closed circuit video performance.
      - Les Levine, "Topesthesia", 1971; 3 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 2, Item 2, Folder 3)
        Multi channel video and sound installation.
      - Bruce Nauman, "Studio Tape with Two Cameras", 1971; 2 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
      - Michael Netter, "Brigid Polk at the George Washington Hotel", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Eric Siegel, "Psychidelivision II", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Robert Whitman, "Clock", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 12, Folder 7)
        Recorded artifact of interactive multimedia installation.
  - "Betty Parsons' Private Collection" (1968) (Box 12)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Catalog, Press Release, and Clippings, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Photograph of Parsons, circa 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Boris Lovet-Lorski: Art Deco Sculpture" (1972-1973) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms, Lists, and Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Photographs and Notes, circa 1972 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Chance and Choice" (not realized), Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Colin Greenly: Intangible Sculpture" (1974) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Grant Documentation, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Insurance and Bills, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Notes and Writings, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Printed Material and Photographs, 1966-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - "Collages by Lee Gatch" (1973) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Publicity, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - "Constructivist Tendencies: Mr. and Mrs. George Rickey's Private Collection" (1972) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 28-29)
    - Lists and Insurance, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Clippings, and Research, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Slides of Artwork, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Destruction Art" (1968) (Box 13)
    - Biographies, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Oversized galleys housed in box 22, folder 4.
    - Clippings, DIAS London, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 24.
    - Clippings, Finch College Museum of Art Exhibition, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, European Artists, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5-7)
    - Correspondence, New York, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Destruction Films, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Manifestos, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Manipulations, A Judson Gallery Publication, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Notes and Research, 1961-1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Artists Performing, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Oversized photograph in box 22, folder 4.
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Flyers, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Oversized flyer in box 22, folder 4.
    - Receipts and Deliveries, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Symposium Information, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "Documentation" (1968) (Box 13)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
    - Catalog Mechanicals, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Catalog Photographs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Labels for Vitrines, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Letters and Photographs Exhibited, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Loan Forms, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
    - Photographs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
    - Press Release, Announcement and Clipping, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Research, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Oversized clipping in box 22, folder 4.
  - "The Dominant Woman" (1968-1969) (Box 13)
    - Article by M. Citron and J. Gelb, "Venus Through the Ages", circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Biographies, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Oversized item in box 22, folder 5.
    - Catalog, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Oversized galleys in box 22, folder 5.
    - Catalog Photographs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Oversized clipping in box 22, folder 5.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 38-39)
      See also under research for additional correspondence with prospective artists for the exhibition.
    - Lists, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Loan Forms, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 41-42)
    - Photographs of Artists, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 44-45)
    - Photographs of Opening, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Receipts and Deliveries, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Research, Correspondence and Photographs, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 49-51)
      Oversized clipping housed in box 22, folder 5.
    - Research, Notes and Writings, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Research, Printed Material, circa 1968 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      Oversized posters in OV 23.
  - "Drawings by New York Artists" (not realized at Finch College), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Ellsworth Kelly" (not realized), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Energy Sculpture" (1965) (Box 14)
    - Catalog Text and Biographies, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Oversized clippings housed in box 22, folder 5.
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - "Finch College Alumnae and Their Husbands" (1969) (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lists and Writings, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets of Opening and Installation, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - "Five Centuries of Graphic Art" (1966) (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Announcement, and Press Release, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Catalog and Announcement Drafts, circa 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1066 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Lists and Receipts, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 16-19)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - "Les Formes Vivantes: Alexander Archipenko" (1965) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Oversized catalog draft housed in OV 25.
  - "Forms in Metal" (1975) (Box 14)
    - Bills, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Catalog, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
    - Installation, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Insurance, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 28-31)
    - Notes and Writings, circa 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)